import { TopicData } from '../types/types';

const animalData: TopicData[] = [
  {
    front: '🧸',
    back: 'Bear',
  },
  {
    front: '🕊',
    back: 'Bird',
  },
  {
    front: '🐱',
    back: 'Cat',
  },
  {
    front: '🐣',
    back: 'Chicken',
  },
  {
    front: '🐶',
    back: 'Dog ',
  },
  {
    front: '🦆',
    back: 'Duck ',
  },
  {
    front: '🐸',
    back: 'Frog',
  },
  {
    front: '🦒',
    back: 'Giraffe ',
  },
  {
    front: '🐴',
    back: 'Horse ',
  },
  {
    front: '🐒',
    back: 'Monkey ',
  },
  {
    front: '🐭',
    back: 'Mouse ',
  },
  {
    front: '🐇',
    back: 'Rabbit ',
  },
  {
    front: '🦓',
    back: 'Zebra ',
  },
];

export { animalData };
